Worapong Rimwungtrakool, Mr. (+66) 89 120-3700 r.worapong@gmail.com

155 Ma-Chareon Road, Nongkheam Bankgok 10160



Twelve years of direct experience in retail business with seven years directly involve in IT and online business from business development, business partnership operations, and actively driving sales and marketing.

Well-rounded in Computers and Smartphones (Software & Hardware) and Online Business including Online Payment and e-Commerce.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

### True Digital Plus Co.,Ltd.

Sep 2014 - recent

Company Business: Online & Mobile Games Publisher and Developer

- **Marketing Manager** Managing and planning all marketing and sales activities for games top up serial sales through dealers;
  - Developing new online payment channels with cost reduction and easy-to-reach for customers; and
  - Building, developing and managing gaming business partner ecosystem.

#### Gamespark Co.,Ltd.

Feb 2012 – Aug 2014

Company Business: Computer hardware and software retailer

**Managing Director** 

- Taking care of all business aspect involved including sales, marketing, purchasing, financial and accounting.

### Neolution Technology Co.,Ltd.

Jan 2011 – Jan 2012

Company Business: Computer hardware distributor

**Product and Marketing Manager** 

- Marketing and Managing the products portfolio;
- Reporting to the CEO regarding sales and various reports on weekly and monthly basis;
- Focusing on High-End international brand products management;
- Revising the company website and developing online marketing;
- Arranging marketing events to expand awareness of products and company.

### Zest Interactive Co.,Ltd.

Sep 2008 – Dec 2010

Company Business: Computer hardware and software retailer

# **Business Development Manager**

- Developing new products line i.e. Gaming Devices;
- Focusing on business development to compete with competitors;
- Re-designing online store;
- Arranging marketing events to expand awareness of products and company;
- Training staffs to improve the work effectiveness.

### **TESCO-Lotus Co.,Ltd.**

Aug 2005 – Jan 2008

Company Business: Modern trade, Hypermarket

### **Marketing Officer - Price Management**

- Tracking and reporting competitors marketing moves involving products and price, arrangement, promotions, which was a part of 'Roll-Back' project;

### **Jusco Department Store**

Mar 2002 – Jul 2005

Company Business: Retail, Supermarket **Department Manager – Fresh Foods** 

- Responsible for all aspects relating to marketing of fresh foods line including forecasting and ordering products to match customers demand, managing lost and shelves life, planning promotions campaign and assure good co-operation with purchasing department;
- Managing human resource in department;

# **EDUCATION** Bachelor of Food Industrial Technology

Silpakorn University, Thailand (1996-2000)

BIRTHDATE 16th October 1978